# Arthur Junio Freitas da Silva

RUA 29-E, Garavelo Park, Goiânia, BR

Phone:

+55 62 982614124

Email:

arthurfscode@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Quasar Flash,** São Paulo, BR — Senior Frontend—Software Engineer

SEP 2020 - PRESENT

Leading, guiding, and coaching a team with three developers.

Creation of a design system using Stitches and Radix. This has resulted in a visually consistent platform that enhances the user experience.

Main techs: JavaScript, React, Typescript, CI/CD, React, Kubernetes, Docker, and AWS.

## **XPORY.COM,** Goiânia, BR — Frontend and Mobile—Software Engineer

DEC 2019 - SEP 2020

Develop and integrate new features for xpory.com e-commerce platform, frontend using React, and mobile using React Native.

Gather requirements with product area and design solutions to achieve business needs.

Main tech: React, React Native, JavaScript, Styled Components, Redux.

### **Interagi Technology,** Goiânia, BR — Full Stack—Software Engineer

MAR 2019 - DEC 2019

Work together with different clients to understand their needs and design tech solutions.

I have gained exposure to diverse technologies and have been privileged to work on high-profile projects for Brazilian government websites, such as CNJ, CNMP, IPEA, and the Brazilian Defense Minister.

Main techs: PHP, React, JavaScript, MySQL

#### **SKILLS**

I have experience with a wide range of tools, including:

React, JavaScript, Node, Typescript, GraphQL, React-Query and Redux

I've applied these skills in multiple companies that I worked.

#### **HIGHLIGHTS**

**Lead** the Frontend team, **Quasar Flash** and **Designed** the new users and admins platforms.

Helped to implement a

Design System that resulted
in a visually consistent
platform, enhancing the user
experience inside Quasar
Flash

Implemented code review and frontend tests culture to the Frontend team.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese, English

# **Ministério Público do Estado de Goiás,** Goiânia, BR — *Software Developer*

JUL 2017 - JUL 2019

Contribute to developing and maintaining a course platform tailored to the needs of lawyers and other intern roles in the Public minister of Goiás.

Main techs: PHP, Javascript, Moodle, Mysql

#### **EDUCATION**

**Delta University** — Bachelor in Information Technology

JAN 2016 - DEC 2020